pioneers.io 2019-12-05

# Pioneers.io

Last modified: 29 Oct 2019

### Welcome to Pioneers.io!

Thank you for using our products and services (“Services”). The Services are provided by startup300 AG, a limited liability company, FN 375689i, ATU67014688, located at Peter-Behrens-Platz 10, 4020 Linz, Austria.

By using our Services, you are agreeing to these terms. Please read them carefully. 

### Definitions

“You” and “your” refer to you, as a user of our Services. A “user” is someone who interacts with, accesses, posts, edits, browses, or in any way uses our Services. 

“We,” “us,” and “our” refer to Pioneers.io.

“User Content” means any personal information submitted in creating a Pioneers.io Account, as well as any information submitted or transmitted to, through, or in connection with our Services, including, but not limited to, research, product plans, business plans, products, services, customers, markets, software, documentation, inventions, processes, designs, drawings, hardware configuration information, business methods, marketing or finances information and/or strategies, digital or photographic images, videos, graphics, text, or audio files.

“Pioneers.io Content” means Content that we create and make available in connection with our Services. 

“Third Party Content” means Content that originates from parties other than Pioneers.io or its users, which is made available in connection with our Services.

“Site Content” means all of the Content that is made available in connection with our Services, including Your Content, User Content, Third Party Content, and Pioneers.io Content.

### Description of Services

We offer a broad range of services and products to individuals, start-ups, companies of various sizes, organisations, governments and other entities. These are viewed, accessed and consumed both physically and virtually through a range of interfaces and devices such as, but not limited to: conferences, events, meetings, open calls, competitions, hackathons, trainings and seminars, masterclasses, our platform and websites at www.pioneers.io, piobay.com, APIs, email services, applications, features, apps, and other technologies. We call these collectively “Service(s)”.

### Who can use the Services

In order to use the Services:

\- you need to be 18 years of age or older;

\- use your real name and the real name of your organisation as well as provide accurate, correct and truthful information;

\- not allow anyone else to use your account or authentication information, or make it known to any other party;

\- be allowed to use the Services under any and all laws that apply to you or our provision of the Services;

\- have the authority to bind any organisation, government or legal entity on behalf of who you use the Services. If these circumstances, you represent, warrant and confirm that you are authorised by such organisation, government or legal entity to use our Services. If you are representing and binding an organisation, government or legal entity to these Policies, all references to “you“ and “your“ will also be interpreted as referring to that entity; and

\- not have had an account with us that was deleted by us due to your violation of these Policies.

If you use the Services, you agree to comply with the Terms of Service.

### Using our Services

You may register as user of the Pioneers.io platform (Piobay). You guarantee that all of the data supplied during registration is accurate.

You may transmit information and content including, but not limited to, files, images, videos, documents, opinions and other material (“Content”) in relation to your use of the Services. 

You represent and warrant that you have the right, title, license or permissions required to submit, provide, upload, make available or interact with a part of your Content through the Services. You also represent and warrant that none of your Content is subject to anyone else’s copyright or other proprietary rights that you do not have a license or permission to use.

You agree, confirm and acknowledge that you may not, at any time, submit, provide, upload or make available any content which, whether in whole or in part:

\- is unlawful, harmful, threatening, defamatory, obscene, infringing, harassing or racially or ethnically offensive;

\- facilitates illegal activity;

\- depicts sexually explicit images;

\- promotes unlawful violence;

\- is discriminatory based on race, gender, colour, religious belief, sexual orientation, disability;

\- is calculated to damage or hinder the operation of the the Services; or

\- is otherwise illegal or causes damage or injury to any person or property.

Do not misuse our Services, do not interfere with our Services or try to access them using a method other than the interface and the instructions that we provide. You may use our Services only as permitted by law, including applicable export and control laws and regulations. We may suspend or stop providing our Services to you if you do not comply with our terms or policies or if we are investigating suspected misconduct.

You may not do any of the following while using the Service:

\- crawl, scrape or otherwise retrieve any data whatsoever except through the interfaces that we support for direct, non-automated use by users, unless specifically permitted by our robots.txt file or explicitly authorised by us;

\- scan or test the Service for vulnerabilities or try to get around authentication unless specifically contracted to do so by us;

\- fake any e-mail message and/or e-mail address to make it appear as if it comes from us;

\- interfere with the operation of the Service in such a way as to degrade use by other users;

\- iframe our website without our prior written permission;

\- link to our website without permission; or

\- suggest any association, approval or endorsement by us if none exists.

Using our Services does not give you ownership of any intellectual property rights in our Services or the content that you access. You may not use content from our Services unless you obtain permission from its owner or are otherwise permitted by law. You may not reproduce, sell or loan the Services. 

These terms do not grant you the right to use any branding or logos used in our Services. Do not remove, obscure or alter any legal notices displayed in or along with our Services.

Our Services display some content that is not Pioneers.io’s. This content is the sole responsibility of the entity that makes it available. We may review content to determine whether it is illegal or violates our policies, and we may remove or refuse to display content that we reasonably believe violates our policies or the law. But that does not necessarily mean that we review content, so please do not assume that we do.

### Modifying and Terminating our Services

We are constantly changing and improving our Services. We may add or remove functionalities or features and we may suspend or stop a Service altogether.

You can stop using our Services at any time, although we would be sorry to see you go. 

Pioneers.io may also stop providing Services to you or add or create new limits to our Services at any time, without providing any indication of reason(s).

### Your Content in our Services

You hereby grant us a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free license and the right to sublicense during your use of the Services and as required for a reasonable time afterwards as set out in these Terms so that we can reproduce, adapt, publish, transmit, process and distribute your Content in any media and distribution method used by Pioneers.io. 

When you upload, submit, store, send or receive content to or through our Services, you give Pioneers.io (and those we work with) a worldwide licence to use, host, store, reproduce, modify, create derivative works (such as those resulting from translations, adaptations or other changes that we make so that your content works better with our Services), communicate, publish, publicly perform, publicly display and distribute such content. The rights that you grant in this licence are for the limited purpose of operating, promoting and improving our Services, and to develop new ones. 

The Services are regularly updated and improved and you agree that the ways in which others interact with your Content will change in accordance with such updates and improvements. You agree that the license you give us to your Content allows us to make your Content available to other organisations and individuals, providing that such use is subject to our Privacy Policies. The license for your Content does not require compensation to you from us.

Our license to use your Content is extinguished when you remove such Content from our Service, although your Content may still be accessible by other users if you have given permission to use your Content in the course of your use of the Service. Your Content will continue to be available for some time in places such as our backups and other users may still have your data when they have created a local copy (for example as a file or hard-copy) that exists outside of the Service or our control, as well as other uses. Please see our Privacy Policy for more information.

You agree that any and all Content that you give, provide, upload or make available to us is not confidential or proprietary in any way whatsoever and you acknowledge and agree that it will not be treated as such by us or any other party that can access it as a result of your use of the Service. For the avoidance of doubt, any and all processing by us of personal data shall be in accordance with the provisions of our Privacy Policy.

### Idea and Feedback Submissions

We welcome all suggestions to improve our Services, ideas, proposals, feedback or other material submitted to us, but we consider them to be helpful advice, freely given. To ensure against any misunderstandings, we want to emphasize that we do not compensate for any ideas, proposals or suggestions provided by you or any users to Pioneers.io. 

Pioneers.io shall not be liable for the disclosure, use or exploitation of such information.

### Communications

You can control most of the communications from us to you through the Service. In some cases, we may need to communicate with you about matters, such as support messages, messages sent in the course of helping you manage your account, updates, service announcements and similar types that you may not be able to opt-out from receiving. These will be sent in accordance with the terms of our Privacy Policy.

### Third Party Content

There are links to many third-party sites and resources on the Platform that are provided by third-parties, which are provided for your information. The presence of any link on the Platform does not mean that we have approved or reviewed them in any way and we make no representation, endorsement or recommendation of such links or their providers. We allow links in the Service to other websites that do not belong to us. The Policies apply only to the Service and not to any other websites, apps - really anything outside of the Service. Each third-party website may have policies different from our Policies and you should read and comply with these policies. We are not responsible for the terms, privacy practices or content of any of these third-parties or any harm you may encounter as a result of misuse of your data.

### Events organized by Pioneers.io

Pioneers.io organizez events and meetings for professionals like, but not limited to: Pioneers annual flagship event, industry-focussed chapter events, consultancy offline programs, meetings, competitions, hackathons, trainings and seminars, masterclasses, Pioneers Ventures offline programs, Pioneers Asia, Pioneers Challenge and others.

Registration for Pioneers.io events and ticket sales are carried out through Eventbrite Inc., 651 Brannan Street, Suite 110, San Francisco CA 94107 (www.eventbrite.com, hereinafter “Eventbrite”). The terms and conditions to be applied for the user are the Eventbrite General Business Terms and Conditions, available at https://www.eventbrite.com/tos/.

You should note that that there is no right of withdrawal as defined in §5f Z. 7 of the Austrian Consumer Protection Act since the provision of services within the scope of recreational activities (§5c, para.4 Z 2,Austrian Consumer Protection Act), which also includes events, is excluded from the right of withdrawal.

Registration for an event does not become binding for Pioneers.io until the full purchase price of the ticket(s) has been paid. In the case of default, the participant is obliged to provide compensation for default interest and all other procedural and non-procedural costs of recovering the debt incurred.

In the case of either the event date or location (event venue) being changed, in general tickets remain valid.

In the case of rescheduling an event, the cardholder’s ticket may be returned by a deadline to be determined by Pioneers.io, preferably immediately after the announcement of the new event date. After the deadline has expired, any claims for reimbursement will expire.

A refund without returning the original ticket is not possible. On returning the ticket, the customer should specify his bank account details and will then receive a refund of the price paid. If the ticket is not returned within the time limit, no refund is possible. Additional claims (e.g. postage, travel expenses, etc.) are excluded.

A refund is only possible up to 14 days before the event, after which a cancellation fee of 50% will be retained.

In the event of a no-show (the ticketholder does not show up at the event), there will be no refund of the ticket price.

The purchase of tickets for commercial resale is prohibited.

Discounted tickets are only valid in combination and/or in conjunction with an authorized identification qualifying for discount. This must be presented when purchasing the ticket and shown on request to gain admission to the event venue. 

For the events, participants’ data can be stored on smart cards (NFC cards).

Pioneers.io reserves the right to exclude persons from their events. Any payments made by a person who is then excluded will be refunded by Pioneers.io.

Pioneers.io is not responsible for personal items that are lost or damaged during events.

Each participant must make provision for their own insurance. There is no coverage either through the organizer and/or Pioneers.io.

Except for personal injury, Pioneers.io is not liable for minor cases of negligence.

### Moving and Still Images Recordings during Pioneers.io events

Within the framework of Pioneers.io events, audio, picture and video recordings of you, any of the individual participants, and the event will be created free of charge. You agree that these recordings and images / photographs, and the unlimited spatio-temporal use can be used free of charge for media reports, advertising purposes on various channels (online, print, TV, radio, outdoor) and in various formats (eg. posters, print ads, online campaigns, moving images, brochures), calendars, commercial products and manuals (eg. future reports, white paper illustrations), and on Pioneers.io websites and third party channels (e.g. TV, Radio, print, outdoor, online such as websites, social media with eg. rights of use for YouTube, Vimeo, Facebook, etc.) and these rights of use may be given to third parties by Pioneers.io, both free of charge and also against payment.

### Data Protection and Privacy Policy

Pioneers.io Privacy Policy explain how we collect, process, store and use your personal data and protect your privacy when you use our Services and interact with us, such as:

\- how we collect information about you;

\- how we use information we collect;

\- how we control your information;

\- how we store and secure your information;

\- how your information is shared;

\- how we transfer your information to other countries; and

\- additional information we think might be useful to you.

By using our Services, you agree that Pioneers.io can use such data in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

You have choices about the use of personally identifiable information which we hold about you. You can access, update and request the removal of the information we hold about you. If you don’t agree with the Policies, please do not access or use the Services, or interact with us. 

**What information do we collect about you?**

_Information you give us._ This includes personally identifiable information that you provide to us when you use the Service by directly inputting it or by other means. including, but not limited to: surname, first name, date of birth, year of company founding, company name, address, email address, websites, country of origin, if applicable: industry, technology, Twitter ID, LinkedIn ID, Facebook ID, profile picture, etc.

Our Services change from time to time so the options for the information you provide (as with other information) may change. Also, the personally identifiable information may vary depending on how you interact with the services. For example, it is possible to create an account using an e-mail or by using a social login, and different types of profiles you use to connect with opportunities may have different items to complete.

**Here are some examples where you may give us personally identifiable information:**

_Account and Profile Information_ \- This includes the name, email address and password you provided at the time of registering for the Service. Please note that we do not store the password in plain text (they are encrypted - salted hashes). It also includes information you input into your profile (including, but not limited to: surname, first name, profile picture, date of birth, year of company founding, company name, address, email address, websites, country of origin, if applicable: industry, technology, Twitter ID, LinkedIn ID, Facebook ID, etc.). Any messages you send or receive, any information you provide to us by other means such as e-mail or forms, as well as any data you provide while using the Service;

_Information you give us when you receive professional services from us_ \- We collect information from you regarding you and your business, including personal income and tax information, identification information for the purposes of compliance with anti-money laundering regulations, and other information as required to fulfil our obligations to you and third parties. We access and store information comprised in submissions made with our assistance to government agencies and organisations, and communications with those agencies by you on your behalf. 

_Information you give us through the Service_ \- You can post, send, access and share information through our Services. For example, you can make notes and comments, send a message asking us to provide a professional service, send a message to other user(s), reply to a message you receive in your e-mail, connect with an opportunity, provide us with feedback or upload a file;

_Information about Gender, Racial and Ethnic Origin_ \- Some members of our community that offer opportunities to other users, such as accelerator programs or start-up initiatives, want to track their progress towards providing opportunities to a range of genders, races or ethnicities. In order to help them do so, we may ask you for information about your gender, racial or ethnic origin. You are not required to provide this information to us - we will always make it optional and we’ll only provide aggregated statistics related to this data. Please be aware that data about racial and ethnic origin is a special category under Article 9 of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (commonly called “GDPR”);

_Information you give when you are asking for support or we are providing it._ You may choose to give us information about a problem you are having, or ask us how to use the Service and in doing so you may provide us with information by e-mail, through live chat, by voice, through third-party platforms or by other means;

_Information you give us so we can collect money from you or send money to you_ \- If you pay us for all or any part of the Service, or if we need to send you money, we may ask you to give us information we require to collect such as bank information, card details, direct debit details, names of people responsible for payment or billing contacts. We do not store payment card details. All payments taken by us are handled by a third party payment processor and whilst our payment pages might look like they are operated by us, they are in fact operated by such payment processor (which we may choose from time to time at our absolute discretion).

_Information we get automatically when you use the Services._ This is personally identifiable information we receive and that is collected by automated systems involved in delivering the Services or when you take specific actions while using the Services.

_Cookies_ \- We and third parties use cookies and other tracking methods to deliver you the Service. 

_Logs and Analysis_ \- We log data about your use of the Service and your response to any communications from us by email or by means of the Platform in order to provide you with the Services, identify issues and understand usage. We do this by means of technology solutions that we have built ourselves and through technologies provided by third parties;

_Information about how you use the Services_ \- We track some aspects related to how you use and interact with Services. For example, we may track the areas of the Service you visit, what you search for, how often you visit us, what devices you use to access the Service, your IP address and location, the URL you enter or exit the Service, data around failures or imperfections that may be triggered when you use the Service and other items.

_Information we get about you from others._ This is information we receive that you do not directly provide when you use the Service. We get it from other users of the Service, third-party services we use to provide the Services, from information we collect and from our partners and vendors in the following circumstances:

_Sign-up and Related Services_ \- If you sign up for the Service, renew your login or request additional services on the Service using your LinkedIn, Facebook, Eventbrite, Twitter, or Google account, you hereby give consent for us to obtain information from those accounts that you approve such as your email address, current employment position, education, profile picture, site traffic and/or location. We also use your IP address to derive an approximate location of where you are using the Service from if none is otherwise provided. The information we get from those services depends on the choices you make in their settings, so please be sure to check those settings before signing up that way. Additionally, some services offer you the choice of what personal data is provided to us and we encourage you to carefully select the information you want to share if that option is available. 

_Other third-party services you may choose to connect to your account_ \- You can choose to authorise us to access information from your calendar, email or other service accounts. For example, you may do this so we can help you find out how you’re connected to other people and try to relate the items to your deal flow tools or other features. If you authorise us to access that information, we receive items such as e-mail sender, receiver information, the content of your and your calendar appointments until you remove our access. If you don't specifically choose to authorise access, we don't get this information. The information we get from these services depends on the settings and permissions you choose, as well as this Privacy Policy that is controlled by the third-party service. We recommend you always check these settings and permissions to understand the information that would be shared with us;

_Scouting_ \- We may collect information directly from you, use public record sources or create editorial content about you or your start-up in order to identify opportunities for you or your start-up. For example, we may engage with you verbally, by e-mail or use other sources to get this information. As further examples, we may provide this information to third-parties to help them scout appropriate startups to accept into a start-up program, identify potential partners or other engage with you;

_Information submitted by other users of the Service_ \- Other users of the Service may provide information about you when they add information during their use of the Service. As examples, an evaluator for a start-up program you’ve connected with through one of our Services may give you a numeric score and write notes about you, another user may provide your e-mail address to invite you to appear on their start-up profile or another user may connect their e-mail account to the Service and give us information related to your correspondence with them. Some other users may add your startup, information they have about you and other related information to their deal flow tools on the Service and also add their information (such as notes, markets or location) to appear along with the information they or you have given us. The information provided by the other user may result in a communication with you;

_Information we get from other partners_ \- We get information about you from third-party partners including those carrying out market research, advertising and lead generation services and who provide us with information about your potential to use our Service and your engagement with us. For example, a third-party may provide us with information because they think you may be be interested in one of our professional services that we may use to contact you.

**How we use the personally identifiable information we collect**

Our use of the personally identifiable information we collect depends on how you use the Services, as well as the settings and preferences you’ve provided to us.

_To provide and personalise the Services_ \- We use information about you to provide you with the Services. This includes logging you in, authenticating you when you login, operating the Services, responding to your use of the Services, maintaining the Services in line with your requests and providing support to you. As examples:

\- your name and profile picture is used to identify you when you connect with or contact other users of the Service;

\- we use your personally identifiable information to personalise the Services, such as identifying opportunities that match with your skills, location, availability and interests;

\- when you connect with other users of the Service, such as a start-up program, and in order for them to evaluate delivering the opportunity you are interested in receiving from them, we provide them with your start-up public information profile, your start-up private information profile, your contact information including e-mail and the profile information for those associated with start-up.

_For online and offline matchmaking_ \- including, but not limited to - (between participants and attendees, participants and companies, business and enterprise), based on data entered by the you.

_In order to provide an integrated experience,_ your information is available across the various aspects of the Service. For example, the skills or interests you enter on your personal profile may be used to help a start-up program you connect with understand what you know how to do as well as identify job opportunities that match you. We believe that this allows us to provide you with an enhanced user experience in respect of the Service;

_To maintain your profiles_ \- We are a community which is based on real identities and so we use your information so that you and the organisations you are associated with can create and maintain profiles in relation to the Service. A profile will be created for you when you first use the Service and many aspects of the Service require a “Startup” or other entity profile. Each profile has options and tools that allow you to customise it with your personal data such as descriptions, educational history, associations and more. We associate you to organizations with which your profile has links and provide you with an option in each profile interface to immediately hide your profile(s) as well as an option to remove your profile from search indexing;

_Providing other users of the Service with information about you_ \- We might also use your personally identifiable information to suggest that others connect or interact with you where we think this might be in your best interests. For example, by connecting you with a user of the Service that is conducting an event in your area, or identifying you as a potential candidate to another user of the Service that is operating a Start-up program or fund;

_To help users direct opportunities to other users of the Service_ \- Some users of the Service provide opportunities to start-ups, founders and developers. These users often use the Service’s deal flow management tools. These tools allow them to access, add, share, manage and analyse information related to the organisations and users that use the Service. Access to personally identifiable information in the deal flow management tools is controlled based on permissions that are set by the organisation and/or users within each organisation using the tools;

_To improve safety and security of the Services_ \- We use information about you to identify suspicious activity, to investigate potential violations of the Policies and to verify user accounts;

_To market, promote and drive engagement with the Services_ \- We use information about your use of the Services, your contact information and other personally identifiable information about you to send you communications that may be of specific interest to you. This type of use has the goal of alerting you when there are events in respect of the Services which we think you’d like to know about, or to provide information, products and services we think you may be interested in. You can control what communications we provide to you in the settings section of the Services, which includes the option to unsubscribe from all communications from us other than core service messages and system functions, such as password reset;

_To provide you with support_ \- We use your personally identifiable information to resolve issues you have using the Services and to reply to your requests;

_In relation to our legal rights and legitimate business interests_ \- We will use personally identifiable information about you as required by law and when we believe it is necessary to protect our legal rights/interests, the rights/interests of others and in relation to any legal claim, regulatory requirements, audits, disclosures in the event of an acquisition, merger or sale and compliance activities;

_When you give us your consent_ \- You can give us your consent to use your personally identifiable information in a way that is or is not covered by this Privacy Policy or any of the other Policies;

_To generate research and reports_ \- We write and publish information, articles and content in relation to start-ups, industries, markets and other areas related to our community. This might include information we hold about you that you have provided that is generally visible in the Services (such as name, tag-line and location), information we generate on our own or aggregated anonymised data derived in part from your own personally identifiable information;

_For marketing purposes_ \- This means advertising, commercial affiliation, interacting with social media, remarketing and behavioural targeting, interacting with online survey platforms and public relations;

_To improve the Services_ \- We use feedback, aggregated data and may use your information as well to make the Services work better, faster, more securely and more in line with user needs. 

_To communicate with you about the Services_ \- We use information about your use of the Services, your contact information and other personally identifiable information to send you transactional communication that relate to your use of the Services. As examples, we may send you communication by e-mail or other means when you receive a message from another user of the Services. You can control what communications we send to you in the Settings section of the Services, which includes the option to unsubscribe from all communications other than core service messages and system functions like password reset.

**Right to withdraw your consent**

You have the right to withdraw your consent to use your personally identifiable information for a specific purpose at any time. Removing your consent will not change any processing that has already occurred. If you do withdraw your consent, and if we do not have another legal basis for processing your personally identifiable information, then we will stop processing your personal data. If we do have another legal basis for processing your personally identifiable information, then we may continue to do so subject to your legal rights. If we are processing your personally identifiable information because we or a third-party have a legitimate interest you have the right to remove consent, but this may mean that it is no longer possible for you to use the Services.

**How we share information we collect**

Sharing and Collaborating with other users in the Services’ community

When you connect with other users of the Services - When you connect with another Service user, you give them permission to see, share, edit, copy and download information you add to the Services. Examples of connections include applying to a start-up program, to meet them during an event, getting a ticket to an event, completing a survey, adding information to our deal flow tools, requesting professional services and more. Some community and collaboration features of the Services show all or some of your profile information when you share or interact with content or other users through the Services. You can provide information that is freely visible to other users, such as the information on your personal profile. 

You can control the visibility of your freely visible profile information, including hiding your profile from other users, using tools we provide you in the “Edit Profile” section of your personal profile.

Please note that hiding your profile will mean that your profile will no longer be visible, but your personally identifiable information will still be visible to other Service users you have given the ability to see your personally identifiable information.

Survey Registration Pages - You may be asked to complete a registration or survey by another Service user. For example, if you choose to complete the team registration for an event that you are attending you can provide your team members' information and technology products you use which will result in your information being shared with the Service user that corresponds to the team registration.

**Sharing with third-parties**

_When we need to comply with applicable laws and requests_ \- When we believe that sharing your personally identifiable information with third-party is required to comply with an applicable law, regulation or request by a government entity, to protect ourselves, our users or others from harm or illegal actions, to respond to an emergency that threatens a person, to fulfil your support requirements and/or to generally protect the security and integrity of the Service.

_Our Partners_ \- Partners help us deliver some parts of the Services. For example, they create opportunities for startups and entrepreneurs such us innovation programs, incubation or acceleration programs, hackathons or other events. 

_Service Providers_ \- We share information with third-parties in order provide, market, improve and support the Services, and these third-party service providers are essential to us in providing you with the Services. This includes service providers that perform services for us such as IT development, data hosting, e-mail delivery, testing, analytics, support infrastructure and other areas. The use of these services requires the relevant third-party to access or use personally identifiable information about you. We monitor these third-party service providers carefully and have policies and procedures in place to maintain the security of your information.

_With your consent_ \- We share your information with third-parties when you give us your explicit consent to share it.

With regard to sharing your data with other Service users and third-parties, please note that we will comply with your requests with regard to all future access to your information but your requests will not apply to any existing off-line information held by another Service user. As an example, when you connecting to a start-up program through an application profile or populate your personal profile some other Service users have the ability to access your information through functionality such as a file data download, printing as a paper version, accessing it by API and other means.

**Giving us information about other people**

You confirm that you have the right to authorise us to process information you give us about other people on your behalf in accordance with this Privacy Policy. As an example, you can give us information about employees of your start-up, business or other entity.

**Sensitive Data**

We do not collect any “Special Category Data” about you except where you provide it to us, or where it is necessary to do so to comply with the law. 

**Data Retention**

We apply data retention policies in line with the type of personally identifiable information retained. We retain personally identifiable information or no longer than is required for our legitimate processing purposes. After a data retention period has expired, we either delete or anonymise your personally identifiable information.The retention policies we apply to different types of personally identifiable information are:

_Your Account Information_ \- This personally identifiable information is retained as long as your account is active and you have not requested its deletion, and nor has it been deleted under the Policies. We may keep some of your personally identifiable information to the extent needed to be in compliance with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes and enforce any agreements we have with you;

_Information you have shared on the Services_ \- We retain personally identifiable information from deleted and deactivated accounts as required to allow other users of the Services to continue to make use of the Services. For example, (i) your name will continue to appear on any messages you have sent to other users of the Services after account deletion and any posts you have made will continue to appear, or (ii) where your name or other personally identifiable information has been added to the Service by you or another user other than in association with your account (such as where your name has been added, with authority, as the founder of a startup and such record is not specifically linked to your account). You acknowledge and confirm that this may result in certain personally identifiable information remaining on the Service in these circumstances.

Apart from what we’ve described above, we’ll archive and stop actively using any personal identifiable information about you within a reasonable length of time (usually one year) of your last use of the Service. We’ll do our best to make it happen more quickly. We’ll also delete your personal data from our archives within one year from your last use of the Services in respect to all use of the Services other than professional services. Due to our compliance obligations, for professional services we’ll delete your personal data from our archives within ten years from your last use of the Services.

**How we store your information**

We collect information globally and store that information in the European Union (Vienna, London and Frankfurt) on our own servers and that of our service providers as part of providing the Services. These service providers are based inside the European Economic Area. We do not store or transfer personally identifiable information outside the EEA.

**Security of your information**

We take security of your data seriously and work hard to avoid loss, misuse, unauthorised access or disclosure. No security system is perfect and despite our efforts and the distributed nature of the Internet, we can’t guarantee that your personal data will be absolutely secure, either while it is being transmitted or while stored on our systems. 

**Access and Control of your Information**

You have rights with respect to your personally identifiable information. We have compiled a list of choices below that you may make with additional information on how to make them happen.

You have the right to:

\- request access to personally identifiable information we hold about you;

\- deactivate your account;

\- update your personally identifiable information;

\- delete your personally identifiable information;

\- ask us to stop using your personally identifiable information;

\- ask us not to use your personally identifiable information to profile you or make automated decisions about you;

\- stop receiving communications from us; and

\- ask us to port your data to another service provider if technically feasible, or to provide you with a copy of personally identifiable information we hold about you in a structured, electronic format.

You can accomplish most of these directly using the tools we provide to you as part of the Service. If you are unable to do so using the tools we provide, please contact our support through the help section of our website, or e-mail us at support@pioneers.io. Depending on the choices you make, it may not be possible for us to continue to provide you with the Services after we implement your choices. This may result is us closing your account or your use of the Services being limited or not possible.

### Warranties and Disclaimers

We are committed to deliver our Services and contents to you with the highest professional standard and constant availability. We cannot guarantee, however, that Services: 

\- will be always be free from defects, inaccuracies or errors, 

\- always available, 

\- will meet your requirements,

\- will operate in the configuration or with other hardware or software you use.

In addition, we may stop (permanently or temporarily) providing the Services (or any features within the Services) to you or to users generally and may not be able to provide you with prior notice.

Other than as expressly set out in these terms or additional terms, neither Pioneers.io nor its suppliers or distributors makes any specific promises about the Services. For example, we do not make any commitments about the content within the Services, the specific functions of the Services or their reliability, availability or ability to meet your needs. We provide the Services on an “as is” and “as available” basis. 

### Liability for our Services

When permitted by law, Pioneers.io and Pioneers.io’s suppliers and distributors will not be responsible for lost profits, revenues or data, production, anticipated savings, business, contracts, commercial opportunities, goodwill, or indirect, special, consequential, exemplary or punitive damages.

No advice or information, whether oral or written, obtained from the Services provided by us, will create any warranty not expressly made herein. Your use or reliance on any Content or other information, material, views or opinions in, or in relation to, the Services is at your own risk. You should exercise good judgement and caution as many individuals and entities add their information to the Service and we do not represent, warrant or guarantee in any way whatsoever that anything in the Service is reliable, accurate, correct, accurate or truthful. Content on the websites is the sole responsibility of those that submit it and can be harmful, incorrect, inappropriate or offensive.

In all cases, Pioneers.io and its suppliers and distributors will not be liable for any loss or damage that is not reasonably foreseeable.

### Business uses of our Services

Technically, Pioneers.io cannot determine with certainty whether a logged-on user of the Pioneers website de facto represents the person/company that the user/the company purports to be. Pioneers.io therefore shall not assume any liability whatsoever for the actual identity of a user. Each and every user is solely responsible for personally verifying the authenticity of other users.

If you are using our Services on behalf of a business, that business accepts these terms. It will hold harmless and indemnify Pioneers.io and its affiliates, officers, agents and employees from any claim, action or proceedings arising from or related to the use of the Services or violation of these terms, including any liability or expense arising from claims, losses, damages, judgements, litigation costs and legal fees.

### Customer support

Pioneers.io is available by email at support@pioneers.io to address any issues you may have regarding your use of the Services. Most concerns can be quickly resolved in this manner.

### Changes to Terms of Service

We may update these Terms from time to time. You understand and agree that your access to or use of our Services is governed by the Terms effective at the time of your access to or use of our Services. If we make material changes to these Terms, we will notify you by email or by posting a revised version of the Terms on our Site. We will also indicate at the top of this page the date that revisions were last made. You should revisit these Terms on a regular basis as revised versions will be binding on you. You understand and agree that your continued access to or use of our Services after the effective date of modifications to the Terms indicates your acceptance of the modifications.

### Miscellaneous

Court of Jurisdiction is the relevant court in 1010 Vienna. Contractual relationships with Pioneers.io are subject exclusively to Austrian law, excluding the CISG (United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods). Contract language is exclusively German.
